A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.38 (A2013) FA473
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2013.099: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1973-2011; AC_2013_099; 26.2 Cubic Feet 20 standard record storage boxes, R4185-R4204; 20 standard record storage boxes, R4185-R4204
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC_2013_099_2; 22.27 Cubic Feet 17 record storage boxes
    - 2002 CC 189 - ANGKOR DANCE TROUPE - TRAINING FOR AT-RISK CAMBODIAN YOUTH IN LOWELL, MASSACHUSETTS, 2002-2005 (Box R4203)
    - 2013.099.114 - 2002 CC189 - Angkor Dance Troupe 50845 - Audiovisual, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:099:114)
    - 2002 CC 190 - ARTSCORPSLA - "SPIRALING ROOTS", 2002-2006 (Box R4203)
    - 2002 CC 191 - GLOBAL ACTION PROJECT - DOCUMENTARY PROJECT FOR REFUGEE YOUTH, 2002-2005 (Box R4203)
    - 2013.099.112 - 2002 CC191 S - Politicas de Indentidades y Diferencias Sociales en Tiempos de Globalization - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:099:112)
    - 2013.099.113 - 2002 CC191 - Politicas de Cuidania y Sociedad en Tiempos de Globalization - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:099:113)
    - 2013.099.115 - 2002 CC191 - One Family World Refugee Day PSA Picture a Story - Audiovisual, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:099:115)
    - 2013.099.116 - 2002 CC191 - Moving On - Audiovisual, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:099:116)
    - 2002 CC 192 - CHINESE THEATRE WORKS - "DAY JOBS AND OPERA DREAMS", 2002-2005 (Box R4204)
    - 2002 CC 193 - CORNERSTONE THEATER CO. - BLACK AIDS/BLACK FAITH PROJECT, 2002-2005 (Box R4204)
    - 2002 CC 194 - SOUTHEAST COMMUNITY COLLEGE - "HARLAN COUNTY PROJECT", 2002-2007 (Box R4204)
    - 2002 CC 195 - MUSEUM OF CLAY (PARAGUAY) - RESIDENT FELLOWS, "IDENTITIES IN TRANSITION" (VISUAL ARTS CENTER) (2 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 1998-2005 (Box R4204)
    - 2013.099.155 - 2002 CC195 - "Las Institucioes del Arte (la agenda critica) - Oversize, 1998-2005; 2013:099:155 (Box SF7)
    - 2013.099.121 - 200 CC195 - Escruituras en Transito: Textos del Seminario/Primera Parte - Published Material, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:099:121)
    - 2013.099.122 - 2002 CC195 - Escrituras en Transito: Textos del seminarioes/Segunda Parte - Published Material, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:099:122)
    - 2013.099.123 - 2002 CC195 - Una Interpretacion de las Artes Visuales en el Paraguay - Published Material, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:099:123)
    - 2013.099.124 - 2002 CC195 - La Belleza de los Otros: Arte Indigena del Paraguay - Published Material, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:099:124)
    - 2013.099.125 - 2002 CC195 - Carlos Colombino - Published Material, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:099:125)
    - 2002 CC 198 - UNIVERSITY OF HOUSTON - INTEGRATION OF RECOVERING THE U.S.HISPANIC LITERARY HERITAGE PROJECT INTO HIGH SCHOOL CURRICULA, 2002-2005 (Box R4204)
- AC.2013.100: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1989-2011; AC_2013_100; 27.51 Cubic Feet 21 standard record storage boxes, R4205-R4225; 21 standard record storage boxes, R4205-R4225
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC_2013_100_1; 27.51 Cubic Feet 21 record storage boxes
    - 2002 CC 200 - UNIVERSITY OF MAINE - OPEN ART NETWORK, 2002-2005 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 203 - (CREATIVITY AND CULTURE) - BC TEAM: US-SAUDI RELATIONSHIP: BUMP IN THE ROAD OR THE END OF THE ROAD, 2002-2008 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 204 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - RESEARCH PLANNING COMMITTEE ON THE ARTS, 1998-2004 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 208 - AMERICAN COUNCIL OF LEARNED SOCIETIES - BURKHARDT FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM, 2000-2006 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 209 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - PARTICIPATION AT SYMPOSIA ON COLD WAR, 2002-2004 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 210 - MEDIA FOR DEVELOPMENT TRUST (ZIMBABWE) - AFRICAN FILM AND TELEVISION SCRIPT DEVELOPMENT FUND (2 FOLDERS), 1997-2005 (Box R4205)
    - 2013:100:001 - 2002 CC 210 - African Script Development Fund, Driving to Glory Stills - digital, 1997-2005 (Box 2013:100:001)
    - 2013:100:002 - 2002 CC 210 - African Script Development Fund, Driving to Glory Stills - Audio/Visual, 1997-2005 (Box 2013:100:002)
    - 2002 CC 211 - WORLD FAITHS DEVELOPMENT DIALOGUE (ENGLAND) - CONVENINGS ON POVERTY REDUCTION STRATEGIES IN AFRICA, 2002-2006 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 212 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - "THE SEPTEMBER 11, 2001 ORAL HISTORY AND NARRATIVE MEMORY PROJECT", 2001-2006 (Box R4205)
    - 2002 CC 213 - CENTRE FOR THE STUDY OF DEVELOPING SOCIETIES (INDIA) - "SARAI" PROGRAM, 1999-2006 (Box R4206)
    - 2013:100:003 - 2002 CC 213 - The Cyberohalla Project - Digital, 1999-2006 (Box 2013:100:003)
    - 2013:100:004 - 2002 CC 213 - The Cyberohalla Project - Digital, 1999-2006 (Box 2013:100:004)
    - 2013:100:005 - 2002 CC 213 - The Cyberohalla Project - Published Material, 1999-2006 (Box 2013:100:005)
    - 2002 CC 214 - INDEPENDENT TELEVISION SERVICE - DIGITAL INDEOENDENCE (DI:03) CONFERENCE, 2002-2004 (Box R4206)
    - 2002 CC 218 - SOUTH AFRICAN-AMERICAN ORGANIZATION - RFK DOCUMENTARY FILM PROJECT, 2002-2004 (Box R4206)
    - 2013:100:006 - 2002 CC 218 - Ripple of hope in the Land of Apartheid - Audio/Visual, 2002-2004 (Box 2013:100:006)
    - 2002 CC 220 - FEMINIST PRESS - "WOMEN WRITING IN AFRICA" PROJECT (1 MINUTE FOLDER and 1), 1991-2009 (Box R4206)
    - 2013:100:007 - 2002 CC 220 - Zulu Women: The Life Story of Christina Sibiya - Published Material, 1991-2009 (Box 2013:100:007)
    - 2013:100:008 - 2002 CC 220 - Women Writing Africa: The Eastern Region - Published Material, 1991-2009 (Box 2013:100:008)
    - 2013:100:009 - 2002 CC 220 - Women Writing Africa: West Africa and the Sahel - Published Material, 1991-2009 (Box 2013:100:009)
    - 2013:100:010 - 2002 CC 220 - Rape of Sita - Published Material, 1991-2009 (Box 2013:100:010)
    - 2013:100:011 - 2002 CC 220 - Women Writing Africa: The Southern Region - Published Materials, 1991-2009 (Box 2013:100:011)
    - 2003 CC 004 - MUSEUM OF NEW MEXICO FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION, "CARNAVAL!", 2002-2005 (Box R4206)
    - 2013:100:012 - 2003 CC 004 - Museum of New Mexico Foundation - Exhibition, "CARNIVAL!" - Still Image, 2002-2005; 2013:100:012 (Box SF5)
    - 2013:100:013 - 2003 CC 004 - Carnival! Promotional Images and Captions - Digital, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:013)
    - 2013:100:014 - 2003 CC 004 - Museum of New Mexico Foundation - Exhibition, "CARNIVAL!" - Oversized/Published Item/Audio-Visual, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:014)
    - 2013:100:015 - 2003 CC 004 - Carnival! - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:015)
    - 2003 CC 005 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - EXHIBITION, "I, TOO, SING AMERICA...", 2002-2004 (Box R4207)
    - 2013:100:016 - 2003 CC 005 - Untitled - Still Images, 2002-2004; 2013:100:016 (Box SF5)
    - 2003 CC 008 - NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY AND CREATIVITY, 1999-2006 (Box R4207)
    - 2013:100:095 - 2003 CC 008 - Beyond Productivity: Inforomation Technology, Innovation, and Creativity - Published Material, 1999-2006 (Box 2013:100:095)
    - 2003 CC 009 - ASIA SOCIETY - BURMESE MUSIC AND DANCE TRADITIONS, 2002-2004 (Box R4207)
    - 2003 CC 011 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION- EXHIBITIONS AT NATIONAL MUSEUM OF THE AMERICAN INDIAN, 2002-2007 (Box R4207)
    - 2013:100:017 - 2003 CC 011 - The Native Universe and Museums in the Twenty-First Century - Published Material, 2002-2007 (Box 2013:100:017)
    - 2013:100:018 - 2003 CC 011 - Native Universe: Voices of Indian America - Published Material, 2002-2007 (Box 2013:100:018)
    - 2003 CC 013 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER, CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - CHINATOWN DOCUMENTATION PROJECT, 2002-2006 (Box R4207)
    - 2013:100:019 - 2003 CC 013 - Ground One Voices of Post 9/11 Chinatown - Digital, 2002-2006 (Box 2013:100:019)
    - 2003 CC 015 - MACQUARIE UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA) - BC CONFERENCE: VALUE AND VALUATION IN THE ARTS AND CULTURE, 2003-2006 (Box R4207)
    - 2003 CC 016 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - CULTURAL EXPRESSION AND INDICES OF SOCIAL WELL-BEING IN PHILADELPHIA, 2001-2005 (Box R4207)
    - 2013:100:020 - 2003 CC 016 - Final Report, October 2005 - Digital EMPTY CASE, 2001-2005 (Box 2013:100:020)
    - 2013:100:021 - 2003 CC 016 - Dynamics of Culture Final Report, October 2005 - Digital, 2001-2005 (Box 2013:100:021)
    - 2013:100:022 - 2003 CC 016 - CD ROM - Social Impact of the Arts Projects - Digital, 2001-2005 (Box 2013:100:022)
    - 2013:100:023 - 2003 CC 016 - PENN Social Impact of the Arts Project, Dynamics of Culture, Final Report, October 2005 - Digital, 2001-2005 (Box 2013:100:023)
    - 2003 CC 017 - MINNEAPOLIS INSTITUTE OF ARTS - EXHIBITION, "ART OF THE NORTHERN PLAINS: THE WHITE CLAY PEOPLE", 2002-2010 (Box R4207)
    - 2013:100:024 - 2003 CC 017 - "From Our Ancestors: Art of the White Clay People" Database - For Final Report on Grant 2003 CC 017 - Digital, 2002-2010 (Box 2013:100:024)
    - 2013:100:025 - 2003 CC 017 - From Our Ancestors: Art of the White Clay People - Published Material, 2002-2010 (Box 2013:100:025)
    - 2003 CC 018 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART - EXHIBITION OF WORKS OF KERRY JAMES MARSHALL, 2002-2004 (Box R4208)
    - 2013:100:026 - 2003 CC 018 - Slides - Still Image, 2002-2004; 2013:100:026 (Box SF5)
    - 2003 CC 019 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, LOS ANGELES - "A VER: A REVISIONING OF ART HISTORY", 2002-2005 (Box R4208)
    - 2003 CC 021 - NEW ENGLAND FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - CAMBODIAN ARTISTS PROJECT, 2003-2005 (Box R4208)
    - 2003 CC 022 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN-MILWAUKEE - "ART AND POLICY: MAPPING THE FIELD" PROJECT, 2003-2005 (Box R4208)
    - 2003 CC 023 - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY - SYMPOSIUM ON CONTEMPORARY ASIAN AMERICAN VISUAL ART, 2003-2005 (Box R4208)
    - 2003 CC 024 - JOHNS HOPKINS UNIVERSITY - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS, "THE CHILD ON THE WING...", 2002-2009 (Box R4208)
    - 2013:100:027 - 2003 CC 024 - Johns Hopkins - Digital, 2002-2009 (Box 2013:100:027)
    - 2013:100:028 - 2003 CC 024 - The Sanganayi Project: Too Late to go Back - Digital, 2002-2009 (Box 2013:100:028)
    - 2003 CC 025 - UNIVERSITY OF NOTRE DAME - RESIDENT FELLOWSHIPS (JOAN B. KROC INSTITUTE FOR INTERNATIONAL PEACE STUDIES) (2 FOLDERS), 1999-2007 (Box R4208)
    - 2003 CC 027 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS - STUDY OF TRANSNATIONALISM IN SAN ANTONIO (SAN ANTONIO), 2001-2005 (Box R4209)
    - 2003 CC 028 - UINVERSITY OF NORTH CAROLINA, GREENSBORO - EXHIBITION, "BORNE OF NECESSITY", 2003-2004 (Box R4209)
    - 2003 CC 029 - WING LUKE MEMORIAL FOUNDATION - PROJECT, "IMMERSION EXHIBITIONS" (1 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 2002-2005 (Box R4209)
    - 2013:100:029 - 2003 CC 029 - Still Image, 2002-2005; 2013:100:029 (Box SF5)
    - 2003 CC 031 - AMERICAN LIBRARY ASSOCIATION - LIBRARIES AND INFORMATION COMMONS WORKSHOP, 2003-2005 (Box R4209)
    - 2003 CC 033 - NATIONAL INTERFAITH HOSPITALITY NETWORK - "BUILDING UNDERSTANDING THROUGH INTERFAITH ACTION" PROGRAM, 2001-2005 (Box R4209)
    - 2003 CC 034 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (CENTER FOR FOLKLIFE AND CULTURAL HERITAGE), 2002-2008 (Box R4209)
    - 2003 CC 035 - UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS, CHICAGO - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (LATIN AMERICAN AND LATINO STUDIES PROGRAM), 2002-2008 (Box R4209)
    - 2003 CC 036 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS, "HOW DO THE POOR CONSTITUTE COMMUNITY?", 2002-2008 (Box R4210)
    - 2003 CC 037 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - "REPORTING THE ARTS II", 2002-2005 (Box R4210)
    - 2013:100:030 - 2003 CC 037 - Reporting the Arts II: News Coverage of Arts and Culture in America - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:030)
    - 2003 CC 038 - AMERICAN UNIVERSITY - STUDY ON IMAGINATION, CREATIVITY AND CONTROL IN INDEPENDENT FILMMAKING, 2003-2005 (Box R4210)
    - 2013:100:031 - 2003 CC 038 - Untold Stories: Creative Consequences of the Right Clearance Culture - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:031)
    - 2003 CC 040 - SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTION - "MEKONG LIFEWAYS" PROJECT, 2001-2005 (Box R4210)
    - 2013:100:032 - 2003 CC 040 - Bamboo on the Mountains - Digital, 2001-2005 (Box 2013:100:032)
    - 2003 CC 041 - ARAB COMMUNITY CENTER FOR ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL SERVICES - EXHIBITION, "CROSSING BOUNDARIES: ARAB AMERICAN ARTISTS IN THE UNITED STATES", 2003-2005 (Box R4210)
    - 2013:100:033 - 2003 CC 041 - Slides, 2003-2005; 2013:100:033 (Box SF5)
    - 2003 CC 042 - ARTRAIN USA - EXHIBITION, "NATIVE VIEWS: INFLUENCES OF MODERN CULTURE", 2002-2004 (Box R4210)
    - 2003 CC 043 - MATTRESS FACTORY - INSTALLATIONS BY CUBAN ARTISTS, 2003-2005 (Box R4210)
    - 2013:100:034 - 2003 CC 043 - Mattress Factory - Installation by Cuban Artists- Still Image, 2003-2005; 2013:100:034 (Box SF5)
    - 2013:100:040 - 2003 CC 043 - New Installations, Artists in Residence: Cuba- Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:040)
    - 2003 CC 044 - OAKLAND MUSEUM/MUSEUM OF CLAIFORNIA FOUNDATION - EXHIBITION, "NEXT STOP VIETNAM: CALIFORNIA AND THE NATION TRANSFORMED", 2003-2005 (Box R4210)
    - 2013:100:117 - 2003 CC 044 - Oakland Museum - Slides, 2003-2005; 2013:100:117 (Box SF5)
    - 2013:100:035 - 2003 CC 044 - Oversized, 2003-2005; 2013:100:035 (Box SF7)
    - 2013:100:036 - 2003 CC 044 - Oakland Museum Orientation Theater - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:036)
    - 2013:100:037 - 2003 CC 044 - Oakland Museum Hollywood and Vietnam - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:037)
    - 2013:100:038 - 2003 CC 044 - What's Going On? - California and the Vietnam Audio Tour Highlights - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:038)
    - 2013:100:039 - 2003 CC 044 - What's Going On? - California and the Vietnam Era - Published Material, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:039)
    - 2003 CC 045 - MUSEUM OF CONTEMPORARY ART, SAN DIEGO - EXHIBITION, "STRANGE NEW WORLD...", 2003-2007 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 046 - LA RAZA GALERIA POSADA - EXHIBITION ON ROYAL CHICANO AIR FORCE, 2003-2007 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 048 - CENTER FOR ARTS AND CULTURE - PROGRAM SUPPORT; RESEARCH ON CREATIVE SECTOR, 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 049 - VERMONT FOLKLIFE CENTER - EXHIBITION, "WEAVINGS OF WAR", 2002-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:041 - 2003 CC 049 - Peter Klosky Sample Exhibit - Inside Lab - Still Image, 2002-2005; 2013:100:041 (Box SF5)
    - 2013:100:042 - 2003 CC 049 - Weaving of Oval Installation Shots - Digital, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:042)
    - 2013:100:043 - 2003 CC 049 - Weaving of War: Fabrics of Memory - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:043)
    - 2003 CC 050 - CURIOUS THEATRE CO. - "THE SPEER PROJECT", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 051 - AXIS DANCE CO. - NEW DANCE WORK, 2003-2004 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 052 - BANG ON A CAN - NEW WORK, 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:044 - 2003 CC 052 - Elida: Iva Bittova-Band on a Can - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:044)
    - 2003 CC 053 - BIG ART GROUP - "HOUSE OF NO MORE", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 054 - CARPETBAG THEATRE - "SOUTHERN SANKOFA, FLYING HOME", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:046 - 2003 CC 054 - Rockefeller - Sankofa Sampler - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:046)
    - 2003 CC 055 - CENTER FOR CULTURAL EXCHANGE - CREATION AND PRODUCTION OF "REORIENTALISM", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:045 - 2003 CC 052 - reOrientalism: Original Cast Recording - Digital, undated (Box 2013:100:045)
    - 2003 CC 056 - CENTER FOR PUPPETRY ARTS - "AVANTI DA VINCI", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 057 - CHILDREN'S THEATRE CO. - NEW SITE-SPECIFIC WORK, 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 058 - CLUBBED THUMB - "DEMON BABY", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 059 - CORNERSTONE THEATER CO. - "THE MUSLIM PROJECT", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:047 - 2003 CC 059 - "You Can't Take it with You" Cornerstone Theater Co. - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:047)
    - 2003 CC 060 - DANSOLOGY - MULTI-MEDIA COLLABORATION, "DEADMANDANCING", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 061 - DIVERSEWORKS - "THE BLACK FACTORY", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:048 - 2003 CC 061 - William Pope L 2004 - How Can You Buy Blackness When it Grows on Trees (Black Factory Video) - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:048)
    - 2003 CC 062 - LA DONNA DANCE - "FLOATING FROM MY HAND", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 063 - FIVE MYLES - "LEM", 2003-2004 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 064 - FLYAWAY PRODUCTIONS - "THE GRIM ARITHMETIC OF WATER", 2003-2004 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 065 - GAMETOPHYTE - MULTIMEDIA PERFORMANCE INSTALLATION, 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 066 - HEADLONG DANCE THEATER - "HOTEL POOL", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2013:100:049 - 2003 CC 066 - Headlong Dance Theater Hotel Pool - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:049)
    - 2003 CC 067 - INTA - '"TREE", 2003-2005 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 068 - KITCHEN (THE) - "THE SLUGBEARERS OF KAYROL ISLAND", 2003-2008 (Box R4211)
    - 2003 CC 069 - LOWER MANHATTAN CULTURAL COUNCIL - "MESSA DI VOCE", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 070 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - "BIRD BRAIN", 2003-2004 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 071 - NEW YORK THEATRE WORKSHOP - NEW PLAY, "MOTHERF**KER", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 072 - OTHER MINDS - "THE GAMELAN CONCHERTO PROJECT", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2013:100:050 - 2003 CC 072 - Gamelan/Symphony rehearsal at SFSU - January 2004 - Audio/Visual, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:050)
    - 2003 CC 073 - PAINTED BRIDE ART CENTER - MUSICAL THEATER WORK, "TWO FOR TEN", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 074 - PERFORMANCE SPACE 122 - "COMING OUT OF THE NIGHT WITH NAMES", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 075 - PREGONES TOURING PUERTO RICAN THEATRE COLLECTION - "RED ROSE PROJECT", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2013:100:051 - 2003 CC 075 - Regina Garcia Scenic and Costume Designer Prefones Theater's the Rose Rose: Images and Renderings - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:051)
    - 2003 CC 076 - RIPE TIME - "INNOCENTS", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 077 - SENS PRODUCTION - "NOIR", 2003-2004 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 078 - SOHO REPERTORY THEATRE - "SUITCASE", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 079 - ENSEMBLE SOSPESO - NEW WORK BY COMPOSER CHAYA CZERNOWIN, 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 080 - SOUTHERN THEATER - "DREAM HOUSE", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 081 - SQUONK OPERA - "BULL", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2013:100:052 - 2003 CC 081 - Squonk Opera Rodeo Smackdown - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:052)
    - 2013:100:053 - 2003 CC 081 - Squonk Opera Rodeo Smackdown: Excerpts from a live performance - 8 Mins - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:053)
    - 2003 CC 082 - STREB/RINGSIDE - DEVELOPMENT OF NEW WORK, 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 083 - TALKING BAND - "THE PARROT", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 084 - TERE O'CONNOR DANCE - NEW DANCE WORK, 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 085 - THEATER GROTTESCO - "THE MAGIC REALISM PROJECT", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 086 - THEATRE MOVEMENT BAZAAR - "DRY CLEANING", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2013:100:054 - 2003 CC 086 - Dry Cleaning DVD - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:054)
    - 2003 CC 087 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, LOS ANGELES - "REVENANT TECHNOLOGIES", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 088 - UNIVERSITY OF NOTRE DAME - "AVANTI", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2013:100:055 - 2003 CC 088 - Avanti: A Postindustrial Ghost Story - Digital, 2003-2005 (Box 2013:100:055)
    - 2003 CC 089 - WILMA THEATER - "RAW BOYS", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 090 - YOUTH SPEAKS - DANCE PIECE BY CHOREOGRAPHER ROBERT MOSES, 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 091 - Z SPACE STUDIO - "THE PEOPLE'S TEMPLE THEATER PROJECT", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 092 - ZACCHO DANCE THEATRE - "GHOST ARCHITECTURE", 2003-2005 (Box R4212)
    - 2003 CC 094 - FORDHAM UNIVERSITY - NATIONAL SOCIAL SURVEY PROJECT ON CULTURE AND CREATIVITY, 2000-2005 (Box R4213)
    - 2013:100:056 - 2003 CC 094 - Arts, Culture, and the Social Health of the Nations 2005 - Published Material, 2000-2005 (Box 2013:100:056)
    - 2013:100:057 - 2003 CC 094 - American"s Social Health: Putting Social Issues back on the Public Agenda - Published Material, 2000-2005 (Box 2013:100:057)
    - 2003 CC 095 - FORT LEWIS COLLEGE - EXHIBITION, "CIRCLE OF THE SPIRIT...", 2003-2005 (Box R4213)
    - 2003 CC 096 - ASIAN CULTURAL COUNCIL - CAMBODIAN ARTISTS MENTORSHIP PROGRAM, 1996-2007 (Box R4213)
    - 2013:100:058 - 2003 CC 096 - "Mentorship - Apprenticeship Program" Cambodian Network "Council" 1995 - Audio/Visual, 1996-2007 (Box 2013:100:058)
    - 2003 CC 098 - ARTS INTERNATIONAL - GLOBAL CULTURAL EXCHANGE ACTIVITIES (6 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 1998-2005 (Box R4213)
    - 2013:100:059 - 2003 CC 098 - Inroads Africa: Six Performing Artists from Africa - Digital, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:100:059)
    - 2013:100:060 - 2003 CC 098 - Speak of Me as I Am - Published Material, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:100:060)
    - 2013:100:096 - 2003 CC 098 - Speak of Me as I Am - Digital, 1998-2005 (Box 2013:100:096)
    - 2003 CC 098 - ARTS INTERNATIONAL - GLOBAL CULTURAL EXCHANGE ACTIVITIES (6 and 1 SUPPL. FOLDER), 1998-2005 (Box R4214)
    - 2003 CC 099 - NEW YORK FOUNDATION FOR THE ARTS - INTELLIGENT AGENT; NETART INITIATIVE, 2002-2004 (Box R4214)
    - 2003 CC 100 - THING (THE) - WIRELESS MEDIA PROJECT, "THING.CLOUDS", 2002-2003 (Box R4214)
    - 2003 CC 102 - PENTACLE - "HELP DESK" PROJECT, 1997-2004 (Box R4214)
    - 2003 CC 103 - CULTURAL INITIATIVES/SILICON VALLEY - RESEARCH ON ADVANCEMENT OF PARTICIPATORY CULTURAL EXPRESSION, 2002-2005 (Box R4215)
    - 2013:100:061 - 2003 CC 103 - There's Nothing Informal About it - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:061)
    - 2013:100:062 - 2003 CC 103 - Immigrant Participatory Arts - Published Material, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:062)
    - 2003 CC 104 - HARVESTWORKS - INTERACTIVE TECHNOLOGY PROJECT, 2002-2004 (Box R4215)
    - 2013:100:063 - 2003 CC 104 - Harvestworks - Interactive Technology Project, 2004 - Digital, 2002-2004 (Box 2013:100:063)
    - 2003 CC 105 - AMERICAN FRIENDS SERVICE COMMITTEE - TAMEJAVI CULTURAL EXCHANGE PROJECT, 2003-2007 (Box R4215)
    - 2003 CC 106 - FUTURE OF MUSIC COALITION - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND COPYRIGHT ISSUES, 2003-2005 (Box R4215)
    - 2003 CC 108 - UNIVERSITY OF THE WEST INDIES, KINGSTON (JAMAICA) - VISITING SCHOLARS PROGRAM, 2003-2009 (Box R4215)
    - 2013:100:064 - 2003 CC 108 - Bim Writer's Symposium - Digital, 2003-2009 (Box 2013:100:064)
    - 2013:100:097 - 2003 CC 108 - Bim Writer's Symposium - Digital, 2003-2009 (Box 2013:100:097)
    - 2003 CC 109 - LEVERAGING INVESTMENTS IN CREATIVITY - ARTISTS AS ASSETS IN COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT PROJECT, 2003-2007 (Box R4215)
    - 2003 CC 111 - DANCE THEATRE WORKSHOP - INTERACTIVE ARTIST PROJECT EXTRANET AND ARTIST RESOURCE AND MEDIA LABORATORY, 2002-2004 (Box R4215)
    - 2013:100:065 - 2003 CC 111 - Dance Theater Workshop - Digital, 2002-2004 (Box 2013:100:065)
    - 2013:100:098 - 2003 CC 111 - Dance Theater Workshop - Digital, 2002-2004 (Box 2013:100:098)
    - 2003 CC 112 - ONEWORLD INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - ONEWORLD TV PROJECT, 2002-2004 (Box R4216)
    - 2003 CC 113 - LEONARDO/INTERNATIONAL SOCIETY FOR ARTS, SCIENCES AND TECHNOLOGY - GLOBAL CROSSINGS PROJECT, 2003-2005 (Box R4216)
    - 2003 CC 114 - ASSOCIATION OF PERFORMING ARTS PRESENTERS - PROGRAM IMPLEMENTATION PLAN, 2003-2004 (Box R4216)
    - 2003 CC 115 - ASSOCIATION FOR CULTURAL EQUITY - DIGITAL PRESERVATION OF ALAN LOMAX VIDEO ARCHIVES, 2003-2004 (Box R4216)
    - 2003 CC 116 - COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY - INTERNATIONAL NETWORK EXPLORING HUMAN RIGHTS AND RELIGIOUS PARADIGMS OF SOCIAL JUSTICE, 2003-2005 (Box R4216)
    - 2003 CC 117 - APPALSHOP - "POVERTY TOUR", 2002-2005 (Box R4216)
    - 2013:100:066 - 2003 CC 117 - RFinEKY Sept. 8-11, 2004 Slide Show - Digital, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:066)
    - 2013:100:067 - 2003 CC 117 - Robert Kennedy Tour -Audio/Visual, 2002-2005 (Box 2013:100:067)
    - 2003 CC 118 - ART START - "DE-CIPHER" PROJECT, 2003-2004 (Box R4216)
    - 2013:100:068 - 2003 CC 118 - Art Start Da-Cyp-her-2004 - Digital, 2003-2004 (Box 2013:100:068)
    - 2003 CC 119 - CITY LORE: THE NEW YORK CENTER FOR URBAN FOLK CULTURE - "POETRY DIALOGUES", 2003-2008 (Box R4216)